var quizData = {
    albacore: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What's the Phylum of Albacore?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            },
            {
                question: "What's the Family of the Albacore?",
                answer: "Scombridae"
            },
            {
                question: "What's Albacore Adult's Mass?",
                answer: "33 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    australianBass: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Australian Bass?",
                answer: "Percichthyidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is The Australian Bass Scientific Name?",
                answer: "Percalates Novemaculeata"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the Australian Bass Rank?",
                answer: "Species"
            }
        ]
    },
    australianSawtail: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is family of Australian Sawtail?",
                answer: "Catshark"
            }
        ]
    },
    basa: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Basa's Family?",
                answer: "Pangasiidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    blackBream: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Scientific Name Of the Black Bream?",
                answer: "Acanthopagrus Butcheri"
            }
        ]
    },
    blackMarlin: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Rank is the Black Marlin?",
                answer: "Species"
            },
            {
                question: "What Order is The black Marlin?",
                answer: "Istiophoriformes"
            }
        ]
    },
    blueGroper: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Order is Blue Groper?",
                answer: "Labifomes"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Blue Groper?",
                answer: "Labridae"
            }
        ]
    },
    blueMarlin: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Blue Marlins Adult Mass?",
                answer: "94 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    blueTang: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Is the Blue Tangs Adult Length?",
                answer: "25-31 cm"
            },
            {
                question: "What is The Blue Tangs Lifespan?",
                answer: "8-20 years"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the class of the Blue Tang?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    bluefish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Family of Bluefish?",
                answer: "Pomatomidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the Scientific Name Of The Bluefish?",
                answer: "Pomatomus Saltatrix"
            }
        ]
    },
    bonito: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Rank Of the Bonito?",
                answer: "Tribe"
            }
        ]
    },
    brookTrout: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Scientific Name Of Brook Trout?",
                answer: "Salmo Trutta"
            }
        ]
    },
    brownTrout: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Rank of the Brown Trout?",
                answer: "Subspecies"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is Brown Trout?",
                answer: "Salmonidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    candiru: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is 2 Other Names for a Candiru?",
                answer: "Toothpick Fish, Vampire Fish"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is The Candiru?",
                answer: "Trichomycteridae"
            }
        ]
    },
    cisco: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Adult mass Is the Cisco?",
                answer: "1.8 kg"
            },
            {
                question: "What Phylum Is Cisco?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            }
        ]
    },
    commonCarp: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "Where does the Common Carp Lives?",
                answer: "Asia, Europe"
            },
            {
                question: "What Class Is the Common Carp?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    cuttlefish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is The Scientific Name Of the Cuttlefish?",
                answer: "Sepiida"
            },
            {
                question: "What Kingdom Are the Cuttlefish in?",
                answer: "Animalia"
            }
        ]
    },
    europeanEel: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the length Of a European Eel?",
                answer: "60-80 cm"
            },
            {
                question: "What Class is the European Eel?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    europeanPerch: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Is The European Perches Adult Mass?",
                answer: "2.6 kg"
            },
            {
                question: "What Is The Phylum Of The European Perch?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            }
        ]
    },
    garfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Order Is The Garfish?",
                answer: "Beloniforms"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Garfish?",
                answer: "Belonidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    gemfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Order Is The Gemfish?",
                answer: "Scombriformes"
            },
            {
                question: "What is The Gemfishes Scientific Name?",
                answer: "Rexea Solandri"
            }
        ]
    },
    goldenPerch: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Adult Mass Of The Golden Perch?",
                answer: "13 kg"
            },
            {
                question: "What is The Phylum Of the Golden Perch?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            }
        ]
    },
    goldfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "Freshwater Or Saltwater (Goldfish)?",
                answer: "Freshwater"
            },
            {
                question: "What Class Is The Goldfish?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    greatWhiteShark: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Is the Approx. Speed of the Great White Shark?",
                answer: "56 km/h. "
            },
            {
                question: "What is The Adult Mass of The Great White Shark?",
                answer: "520-1100 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    guppy: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family Is The Guppy?",
                answer: "Poeciliidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What Class Is the Guppy?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    hapuku: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family is the Hapuku?",
                answer: "Polyprionidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the weight of a Hapuku?",
                answer: "100 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    iridescentShark: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What phylum does the Iridescent Shark own?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Iridescent Shark In?",
                answer: "Pangasiidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    longtailTuna: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Is the scientific Name of the Longtail Tuna?",
                answer: "Thunnus Tonggol"
            },
            {
                question: "What is another name for the Longtail Tuna?",
                answer: "Northern Bluefin Tuna"
            }
        ]
    },
    mahiMahi: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the family of the Mahi Mahi?",
                answer: "Coryphaenidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the maximum length for the Mahi Mahi?",
                answer: "140 cm"
            }
        ]
    },
    makoShark: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the order of the Mako Shark?",
                answer: "Lamniformes"
            },
            {
                question: "What family is the Mako Shark?",
                answer: "Lamnidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    mandarinfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Class is the Mandarinfish?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            },
            {
                question: "Is the mandarinfish Freshwater or Saltwater?",
                answer: "Saltwater"
            }
        ]
    },
    mulloway: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What rank is the mulloway?",
                answer: "Species"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the scientific name the mulloway owns?",
                answer: "Argyrosomus Japonicus"
            }
        ]
    },
    neonTetra: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What's The Scientific Name For the Neon Tetra?",
                answer: "Paracheirodon Innesi"
            },
            {
                question: "What's The class that belongs to the Neon Tetra?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    },
    oceanSunfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the scientific name for the Ocean Sunfish?",
                answer: "Mola Mola"
            },
            {
                question: "What's Another name for the Ocean Sunfish?",
                answer: "Common Mola"
            }
        ]
    },
    peacefulBetta: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What's The length of a Peaceful Betta?",
                answer: "6cm"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the rank of a peaceful betta?",
                answer: "Species"
            }
        ]
    },
    sailfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Rank is the Sailfish?",
                answer: "Genus"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the mass of a sailfish?",
                answer: "50 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    shortbillSpearfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What's The length of the Shortbill Spearfish?",
                answer: "190 cm"
            },
            {
                question: "What's The Shortbill Spearfish Family?",
                answer: "Istiophoridae"
            }
        ]
    },
    siameseFightingFish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What's the lifespan of the Siamese Fighting fish?",
                answer: "3-5 years"
            },
            {
                question:
                    "What's the scientific name of the Siamese Fighting Fish?",
                answer: "Betta Splenders"
            }
        ]
    },
    sole: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Sole in?",
                answer: "Soleidae"
            }
        ]
    },
    southernBluefinTuna: {
        questions: [
            {
                question:
                    "What is the Scientific Name of the southern Bluefin Tuna?",
                answer: "Thunnus Maccoyii"
            }
        ]
    },
    swordfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is another name for a swordfish?",
                answer: "Broadbills"
            }
        ]
    },
    tarwhine: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Tarwhines order?",
                answer: "Perch-like fish"
            },
            {
                question: "What's the Phylum Of the Tarwhine?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            }
        ]
    },
    trevallies: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the order of the Trevallies?",
                answer: "Carangiformes"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the Scientific Name Of the Trevallies?",
                answer: "Caranx Ignobilis"
            }
        ]
    },
    wahoo: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is Another Name for wahoo?",
                answer: "Ono"
            },
            {
                question: "What family is the Wahoo?",
                answer: "Scombridae"
            }
        ]
    },
    whiteBass: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family Is the White Bass?",
                answer: "Moronidae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the Adult Mass of the White Bass?",
                answer: "1.5 kg"
            }
        ]
    },
    yellowBass: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the Adult Mass of the Yellow Bass?",
                answer: "6 kg"
            },
            {
                question: "What Phylum is the Yellow Bass?",
                answer: "Chordata"
            }
        ]
    },
    yellowTang: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Kingdom Is The Yellow Tang In?",
                answer: "Animalia"
            },
            {
                question: "What Family Is the Yellow Tang In?",
                answer: "Acanthuridae"
            }
        ]
    },
    yellowfinTuna: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What Family is the Yellowfin Tuna In?",
                answer: "Scombridae"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the scientific name of the Yellowfin Tuna?",
                answer: "Thunnus Albacares"
            }
        ]
    },
    yellowtailKingfish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "Where does the Yellowtail Kingfish Lives in?",
                answer: "Red Sea"
            },
            {
                question: "What is another Name for the Yellowtail Kingfish?",
                answer: "Great Amberjack"
            }
        ]
    },
    zebrafish: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What is the scientific Name for the Zebrafiah?",
                answer: "Danio Rerio"
            },
            {
                question: "What's the class for the zebrafish?",
                answer: "Actinoterygii"
            }
        ]
    }
};
